(This program is intended
for viewers aged 18 and over.)
(It may contain content
depicting inappropriate behavior)
(violence, sexual content,
and strong language.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(This series is entirely fictional
and does not depict)
(any real individuals, locations,
organizations, or events.)
♪Birthday but with me♪
♪Every time, it's just me and me only♪
♪What's this feeling? I've got no clue,♪
♪Could it be I'm missing you?♪
♪(Am I missing you?)♪
♪Birthday but with me♪
♪Why is it always happening to me?♪
♪The more it happens, the more I see♪
♪Yeah, it must be♪
(Waroros Market)
(B.S. Brothers On the Go)
(Vlog with Laem)
- We're at the market!
- This is Kad Laung.
- Everything looks so good. Look!
- Look at these coconut rolls.
(Wanna try some?)
Everything looks delicious, right?
My mouth is watering. Look.
(Who's doing what?)
(Confused)
- Oh, is this place famous?
- Here!
That's a famous place.
(What should we get?)
(Isn't this too close?)
Someone's hungry.
Aren't you hungry, too?
I'm starving...
just from following you around.
I see.
(Not over snacks yet)
Hey, P'Three,
what are you standing around for?
(Aw!)
Come with me.
(Soh is away.
It's just Laem now.)
- This one's handsome.
- You again?
Before we head up the mountain,
(Finally, a new cameraman)
I'm going to sacrifice my hair and...
(So cute)
let the new hairstylist have a go at it.
Let's see how my hair turns out
and how handsome I'll look
after the styling.
You'll definitely look good
because I've watched
plenty of YouTube tutorials.
(Styling or struggling?)
Trust me, you'll look stunning.
Don't you worry.
I wasn't worried at all.
You know, with this face,
I can pull off any hairstyle.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
- Alright, let's do this.
- Let's go.
- Starting now.
- Go for it.
One, two, three.
Sh*t!
Are you for real?
Well, you were facing away from me.
How am I supposed to style it properly?
Oh, I see.
Okay. Alright.
P'Three, what are you doing?
Well, didn't you say you couldn't do it
because I was facing away?
Now I'm facing you.
Smooth move, huh?
So, do I look handsome yet?
I'm trying my best here.
I'll just...
let you check the mirror yourself.
No, that's not what I meant.
I was asking if you thought
I looked handsome in your eyes.
Oh, look who's blushing! Gotcha!
I know I'm just too irresistible.
- Maybe not.
- Hey!
I didn't say that.
Don't just jump to conclusions.
My, my, you're becoming
quite stubborn lately.
Where did you learn that from?
- You're so adorable. Come here!
- Ow, P'Three!
- P'Three!
- Come here.
- P'Three...
- Come on!
P'Three...
The fans are going crazy.
Three and Soh are being so lovey-dovey,
leading hundreds of thousands of fans
to subscribe to BS BROTHERS.
The team's popularity...
skyrocketed,
finally overtaking Blue Viper.
A major change is coming to Blue Viper.
As they part ways with Ten,
their long-time substitute player.
Word has it the split
wasn't on the best of terms.
Oh, wait a second.
We have some breaking news.
Breaking, PreawPreaw of B.S. Brothers
is facing a ban
after allegedly violating the rules
with a mountain of evidence.
Will B.S. Brothers be able
to move forward?
(Suspension Announcement)
"PreawPreaw has violated the rules
regarding elo boosting,"
"also known as paid rank boosting."
"The ruling has been made
to penalize the player"
"by suspending her
from all competitions"
"for two years."
Sh*t.
Is this for real, Preaw?
I didn't know. I was just a kid.
I thought I could make some money
by playing games,
so I did it.
But that was only one time.
It was so long ago. I was still a kid.
People somehow dug it back up.
Listen to me.
Even if you only did it once,
it's still a violation.
You shouldn't have
thrown your future away like that.
I'm sorry.
Everyone, please calm down.
Preaw is already upset enough as it is.
As for the mistakes that were made,
we should focus
on finding a solution instead.
Yeah, what's done is done. Let it go.
The real question is...
who are we gonna get to replace her?
Yeah, that's a good point.
Where are we going to find
another Carry like her?
All the talented players have likely
been snatched up by other teams.
And we've got only a month left
until the APL.
To find a replacement for Preaw,
we need someone
whose playstyle matches yours,
and other teams
shouldn't be poaching them.
To put it simply, they've got to be...
the rising star
waiting for their moment.
- We're ready...
I have someone in mind.
Maybe not now.
Who is it?
- One on the rocks, please.
- You got it
Since you got back from Chiang Mai,
you've been nowhere to be found.
How've you been?
Being unemployed
has actually been quite a relief.
Is there a reason
you asked me to meet you here?
There is.
Well...
What would you think
if I were to ask you...
to join B.S. Brothers?
Are you insane?
I just left Blue Viper.
Besides,
would your teammates even accept me?
I'm running out of time here.
We need someone with solid skills
who can gel with us,
and I couldn't think of anyone but you.
I won't argue with you about skills.
But whether I'll fit in
with your team or not,
I don't think I will.
But we've played together before,
haven't we?
At the very least,
you should know better than anyone
how Three and I play.
I'm sure
that you can be the Carry
for B.S. Brothers.
You won't have to be a substitute,
waiting to sub in and out
for someone else.
With me,
you'll be in the starting lineup.
(We are B.S. Brothers)
Are you seriously doing this, Preaw?
Before I became a gamer,
my aunt trained me in this.
I never thought I'd have to use it
for our team today.
Each of you, pick a card
and ask your question.
My question is...
who is Jack bringing in
as a replacement?
And will they be as good as you?
Will they get along with us?
Pretty or not?
Is now really the time?
Wait, what?
I was just asking.
- I'm being serious here.
- Exactly.
I know you wanna know it, too.
The Tower.
You might receive news
you're not prepared for.
- Death?
- We're gonna die?
No.
Bad things will gradually
turn into good ones.
That's good to hear.
The Sun...
Light, growth, and vitality.
The person who's coming...
will be a knight in shining armor.
They're coming to help us.
I'm calling it.
Are you making this up
based on the cards?
- A knight in shining armor...
- You're making it up, aren't you?
Guys,
I've gotten our new Carry.
Your knight in shining armor is here.
You can't get away from me, Three.
Come on, let's go.
Listen to what the others have to say.
Look at that stare.
Are you planning on staring all day?
Go sit down.
Listen to what we have to say.
Wait, where are you going?
Sit down.
Jeez.
Won't say anything?
Should we...
Listen.
P'Jack,
why are you bringing a traitor
into our midst?
Would you guys just listen to me?
What the f*ck do you have to say?
What the hell were you thinking?
You know he can't be trusted.
Wait a minute.
When we were in Chiang Mai,
you already talked to him nicely,
didn't you?
I only agreed to talk to him.
I didn't trust him enough
to let him join our team.
Who knows if he's scheming
with Blue Viper.
As for that, you guys can rest easy.
Ten hasn't been in contact
with Blue Viper
since we got back from Chiang Mai.
I know that to you guys,
he might not seem all that trustworthy.
But with the time we have left,
I don't trust
anyone else's skills but his.
People make mistakes.
But I believe...
that if they're given a second chance,
nobody wants to repeat
the same mistakes.
I'm with Jack and Soh on this.
Just chill out, man.
Think about it carefully.
But if you really don't trust him,
you can have Laem keep an eye on him.
He's like a loyal watchdog.
That way, Ten won't be able
to pull anything on you.
Right, boy?
I can't catch a break.
Are you low-key calling me a dog?
Tell you what.
Let P'Pech make the call
since he's been with us since day one.
He knows exactly
what kind of jerk this guy is.
And if P'Pech insists
on letting him join the team,
then I'll give up.
But I'm sure P'Pech will see it my way.
Welcome to B.S. Brothers, Ten.
I thought that after Preaw got banned,
the team would be in total shambles.
It's a good thing
Ten came to the rescue.
It's what I have to do anyway.
F*ck that.
You got kicked out by your old team.
P'Three,
that's not very nice.
Okay.
Aw!
Looks like even P'Three
is scared of his boyfriend, too.
I'm not scared.
I just respect him.
Oh, I see.
Come on, I'm actually glad
P'Ten joined the team.
He is a beast.
That's right.
He is a legendary Carry
with over ten years of experience.
And besides,
he is already used to the APL stage.
Having him on the team
will give us a huge advantage.
As a new member,
I look forward to working with you all.
Oops, my bad.
- Sorry.
- Ten, are you ten years old or what?
Behave yourself.
Just wait until I find someone
better than you.
Want me to help you find one?
I can even find you a new team captain
while I'm at it.
I hope those two
don't start fighting this early.
You're exaggerating, P'Jack.
Both of them are grown-ups.
I don't think
they'll act like kids and fight.
Damn it, what the hell are you doing?
I told you to fall back!
- Do you even understand?
- It's because you're a coward.
This is why
you always lose to Blue Viper.
We wait for the right timing!
You're an idiot. That's why
you were stuck on the bench.
You're dead weight.
You're the captain,
but you play like trash.
How do you expect to win?
You said you'd be a legendary Carry,
and this is how you play? F*ck off.
F*ck you.
F*ck you!
Oh, Soh...
I'm okay.
Hi, everyone, I'm Soh.
Today, I've been assigned...
to give you
an update on B.S. Brothers' daily life.
Right now, we're at the training camp.
Oh, and we've drawn buddies as well.
What do buddies have to do?
Buddies have to share a bedroom,
look after each other,
and get each other gifts.
Most importantly,
buddies have to love each other a lot.
- You're a coward!
- Play it safe.
- Stop playing it safe.
- Look.
Look at me.
- Huh? Okay, yeah.
- Here, like this.
- Keep going.
- You gotta give it a go.
Tap on the heart.
- Sh*t!
- What?
Cockroaches!
Hey, what the hell was that?
Who did this?
You?
Definitely you, Three.
It's not me!
I was just playing my game.
(I think I hear someone fighting.
Is everything okay?)
- You always play such dirty tricks.
- I...
- I don't hear anything at all.
- I'm not.
Do you have any evidence?
- Here's the evidence!
- Don't fight!
My surroundings are...
very quiet.
- You white-headed prick.
- What the hell are you playing at?
Jeez, stop it!
I think you guys should stop fighting.
- No, you sit down!
- Laem, get out.
- Wait...
- Fine, Laem, stay right here.
- Wait, wait.
- Can you back it up?
- You're so dead.
- Hey!
- Hit him. Go for it!
You two, can you just stop fighting?
Agreed.
- I'm not stopping.
- You've done this way too many times.
Jeez, Laem!
- Get out!
- No, you get out!
Yeah...
Yes, that's right.
No one is fighting here.
We all love each other.
Yes, we do.
(Daily Training Schedule)
Let's warm up with a 1v1 match
and see who's really better.
I could beat you with my eyes closed.
Whoa, you dumbass. Join the match.
- Bring it on, I'm not scared.
- Join the match, then.
- I want a piece of you. Come on!
- You guys, chill.
- Calm down.
- Come on!
So you two are really going to duel?
If you do, this has to end.
But I have a condition.
Whoever lets a swear word slip,
I'm charging one thousand baht per word.
Bring it on.
I'll write it down for you.
You jerk!
Noob. Trash.
You bastard!
Whoa, such a throw.
Sh*t, man.
If you're going to be
such a chicken,
just go and sacrifice yourself to JFC.
- What are you talking about?
- Bingo!
I've got money
for the electricity bill now.
Ow, Jack!
- Jack!
- What?
Can I use your bathroom?
Three's being a dick. He cut
in front of me just to take a dump.
Ow, my eyes sting.
Come here.
- Sh*t.
- I haven't even finished shampooing.
- He did that just to freaking poop.
- Acting like a kid.
That bastard...
Pooping at the worst possible time.
Let me see.
You and Three fight every day.
Don't you ever get sick of it?
And you think I want to fight with him?
He's always provoking me.
He just has a foul mouth.
Why do you even care what he says?
So I guess it's my fault again.
Ten,
I know you're not actually a bad person.
But can you just stay calm for me?
From now on,
if Three says anything to you, tell me.
I'll deal with him myself, okay?
Fine.
But I'm seriously at my limit today.
Three is such a pain.
Who poops at a time like this?
If I stay near him one more second,
I think I'll literally die.
Tonight,
can I sleep in your room?
Hey, it's against the rules.
You know that.
Come on, Jack.
Just don't tell P'Toobtub.
Please, Jack. Just for one night.
Please.
Fine. Whatever.
Really?
Yeah.
Are you tired, P'Three?
Are you stressed about P'Ten?
Exactly.
Just hearing his name
makes my blood boil.
Feeling better now?
Just a little bit better.
I guess this isn't enough.
What should I do?
Or maybe...
I need an emergency recharge.
Time to recharge, P'Three.
I'll be your personal power bank.
Is this a fast-charging system?
I feel fully recharged now.
♪If I'm the only one
who's loving with all my heart♪
♪So many times I've rehearsed the line♪
♪To tell you that I wish you were mine♪
You're not feeling stressed
anymore, right?
Yes, for now.
But I'll probably be stressed
again tomorrow
when I have to face Ten.
P'Three,
can you please keep your cool
with P'Ten for me?
P'Ten...
may just have a bit of a sharp tongue,
but if you don't play into his hands,
I don't think there'll be any issues.
And things will eventually get better.
Okay.
I'll try my best to stay calm for you.
Is that okay?
You're the best, P'Three.
Blame yourself for once
instead of blaming me!
Why should I blame myself?
Blame yourself!
You screwed up!
- Screwed up what, exactly?
- Hey, you *sshole.
You think you're so damn good, huh?
- Yeah, I am that good!
- Then bring it!
- I'm right here!
- Whoa, hey!
Take it easy.
These two don't seem to click at all.
Yeah, dammit.
I even tried scolding them
and talking to them nicely...
This is not working. It's a disaster.
And P'Pech wants us
to film for YouTube as well.
Yeah.
Now everyone's going to see them
fighting non-stop.
They're so full of themselves,
thinking they're the best.
It's just a massive ego clash.
I honestly don't know what to do.
So it's an ego thing, huh?
How about we try this?
Rolling!
Three, two, one.
Hello, everyone.
Today, we are bringing you
a fun little challenge.
It's called...
'Role Swap:
Wow, Can't Believe We're Doing This!'
Playing the same old way
is just too ordinary
since each of us is a "god"
in our own role.
I think it's getting a bit boring,
so we're all going to swap roles
for this match!
Huh? What?
Wait, what is this?
Whoa, what a sudden surprise.
Are you scared, Three?
It's just a game.
What's there to be afraid of?
Who said I was afraid of you, Ten?
- Well, aren't you scared?
- I've been waiting for this, too.
- Then let's do this.
- Bring it on.
- Let's see what you've got.
- Come on.
- Bring it on!
- Bring it.
Come on, dammit.
If there are no objections,
I have a very special rule to announce.
The two players with the lowest scores
must follow the orders of the MVP.
It's a deal, then.
Now, let's start
the random hero selection.
Piece of cake.
I'm fine with any role,
but it'd be great if I got Carry
because then I can show someone
how to do his job.
Good.
That way, everyone will see
that when you're good,
you're good in any role!
My apologies, this kid's
just getting defensive.
My apologies to everyone as well.
Some people are just all talk.
Oh, you want a piece of me?
Come on, just try to be on my level.
Try to play Carry as well as I do.
Real pros don't brag, guys.
Hey!
They're all over me. Come support me!
Yeah, hold on. I'm on my way.
Dammit.
You literally let me die on purpose!
You're freaking cheating.
Nothing I can do about that.
The rules have loopholes.
Just focus on playing better.
Go for it!
See? How can you make it
if you don't stick together?
Losing like an idiot.
Hey, cut that last part out.
Okay.
Hey, dive in! Where is everyone?
I'm right behind you.
Is no one defending the base?
(The Red Team's tower
has been destroyed)
Cut!
What the hell are you doing?
You here to cause trouble or something?
Are you here just to mess with us?
Do you even actually
want to be on my team?
I was only following the rules.
Besides, it's just for a video.
Why the f*ck are you being so serious?
Why the hell shouldn't I be?
During practice,
all you've cared about is yourself.
All you cared about was winning.
Why don't you pay attention
to your teammates for once?
How else am I supposed to feel?
You really never change, do you?
That's why I can never trust you.
Fine, I admit it.
Many times, I just wanted to beat you,
but you can't just blame me
for this time.
Then who the hell should I blame?
The whole world?
So you're never in the wrong, huh?
You're always the only right one.
And that's why
you backstabbed your own friends.
Can you guys just cool it for a second?
Yeah, I'm the *sshole.
But didn't everyone
treat me like sh*t first?
- Especially you, Three!
- What the hell did I ever do to you?
Just say it!
You treated me
like I wasn't even your friend.
You treated me like some kind of joke.
Do you really not realize...
how much of a d*ck you've been
to everyone else?
- If I was a d*ck to you,
- Stop him.
or if I made you mad,
then take it out on me!
Why do you have to involve our friends?
Weren't you even ashamed
when you betrayed us?
Now f*cking say something!
Did you ever once think about us?
I did.
I always did.
But I couldn't take it anymore
after what you did to me!
You won't be satisfied
until you see my life ruined, right?
Yeah, I want to see your life ruined.
- Totally ruined!
- F*ck you!
P'Three!
- P'Three!
- Hey, what are you doing?
Stay out of this!
- P'Three!
- Soh, don't. Let him be.
I wouldn't have cared
if you'd only done it to me.
But why did you have to do that to Jack?
What did he ever do to you?
Is what I did so unforgivable
that you had to hurt everyone around me?
Tell me.
Am I really that much of an *sshole?
I'm sorry.
I was such an idiot.
I really hated you, Three.
I pretended not to care about you
cause I just wanted you
to care about me
and treat me better for once.
That's all it was.
I know...
what I did was f*cked up,
but can you please accept an apology
from an *sshole like me?
I'm sorry.
Why didn't you just tell me back then?
P'Three...
Take it easy.
P'Three!
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry, too.
I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry, man.
Does it hurt?
- Dive in!
- MVP is gonna be mine.
- Go, go! It's chill.
- Watch the Jungle King first.
- Let's go!
- Get in there!
- Jack, watch your HP.
- Let's wrap this up.
- Come on.
- This one's all mine.
- Do it!
- Go for it!
Look, a Penta Kill.
- What? Penta Kill?
- Hey, what do you mean Penta Kill?
- You got five kills?
- Whoa, that's not bad at all.
I'm gonna be the MVP.
It's over.
- Look!
- Who's the MVP?
It's JJack!
Dammit!
Since I'm the winner,
I order you two to swap roles.
Soh will be the big brother,
and Three will be the little brother.
- Little brother!
- That's a great idea.
Little bro!
Come here.
Three,
from now on, don't you dare
be stubborn with me, okay?
Aw, P'Soh!
That was so hot.
Enough!
Can you two just swap back already?
I can't stand him acting all cutesy.
Come on, next match.
I want to be the MVP, too. Come on.
- Kill!
- It's over. Let's end it!
What now?
- Who?
- I'm the MVP, boys!
- Who is it?
- Let me see!
It's Cherish!
See? Laem is back!
Oh, P'Jack.
Hey, I'm older than you.
Have you seen
that one TikTok challenge?
You know, where you act
like a couple for a minute.
And who am I supposed to do it with?
Well, you two
were the losers, so who else?
Fine. Just for a minute, right?
Jack, let's just get this over with.
What do you mean, for a minute?
Make it a whole week!
- You bastard, Laem!
Whoa...
Even just now,
you two were perfectly in sync.
No way, P'Toobtub. I'm not doing it.
Well, Laem is the winner.
You've gotta suck it up and do it.
Alright, since you two
are boyfriends now,
how about saying "babe" for us?
Oh, babe!
- Babe! Babe!
We're not stopping until you say it.
Yeah!
- JackTen! JackTen!
- JackTen!
- Fine, fine! I'll do it.
You guys are unbelievable.
Babe...
Aw, come on!
Aw, "babe."
Shut up!
- Babe...
- Boyfriends and boyfriends.
Get out of here.
The RoV scene
is gonna be shaken up again
now that Three, Jack, and Ten
have finally reunited
after Ten announced his departure
(from Blue Viper,
shocking the entire scene.)
(And the buzz around them)
(is absolutely unstoppable, guys.)
(Their latest video
just hit a million views)
(in less than 24 hours.)
(Their chemistry)
is just perfect.
Keep a close eye on the APL this time
because it's Ten
versus his former team, Blue Viper.
It's gonna be heated and intense,
(and it's gonna be
one hell of a showdown!)
So this is how they wanna do it?
You doing okay?
Are you alright?
Come on. Come here.
Come over here.
Let me see.
Your eyes are all puffy.
Are you alright?
You smell really nice, P'Three.
Can you tell the difference...
between the scent of perfume
and the scent of love?
I think it's more like
the scent of a champion.
Oh, look at you!
You're getting pretty good at this.
Thank you, Soh.
I was just making a joke.
You don't need to thank me for that.
You love being praised, don't you?
Yeah, I'm a sucker for it.
Praise me more. Go on, keep it coming.
Praise me now
so I can float right up to the ceiling.
Thank you for opening up to me that day.
I know that...
stepping out of your comfort zone
wasn't easy at all,
but you still chose to stand by me
and B.S. Brothers.
Do you know that having you on the team
makes this the best version
of B.S. Brothers ever?
That's why
you're the MVP of B.S. Brothers.
P'Three...
If I'm no longer competing
for B.S. Brothers,
would you be mad at me?
Well, if it's your own decision,
I could never be mad at you.
But why are you asking that?
Are you thinking of quitting?
That's not it.
I still have some time for gaming
because my classes
aren't too demanding yet,
but once I hit my junior or senior year,
I'm afraid it'll be a lot harder
to manage my time.
I'm worried that in the future,
I won't be able to
play games like this anymore.
Oh, Derpy Kid.
You really gave me a scare.
Even if you don't play games with me
in the future,
it's totally fine.
All I want is for you
to stay by my side
and let me flirt with you forever.
I was only asking.
I never said
I was actually going to quit.
Either way,
the number one Support for B.S. Brothers
has to be this Derya, obviously.
So, nobody else is allowed to take it.
I've already claimed it.
Claiming the role...
or...
claiming the captain?
I'm...
claiming the role
of the captain's boyfriend.
Look at you.
You're just so adorable.
Get over here.
How would I live without you?
I'm gonna go sit down.
Here.
A pre-match drink before the APL.
Just relax, man.
Just admit
you're trying to get me wasted.
What are you talking about?
It brings back memories, right?
Back when you still played music.
I remember you could play...
all of these songs.
I miss the days you played guitar, too.
Ten...
Let me ask you something.
What do you think about that kiss?
What am I supposed to think?
Are you thinking something?
Yeah, I am.
I get that it's probably
not something worth remembering.
That's why you're acting
like it's no big deal.
But once time passes,
I guess it'll just be
another funny story told over drinks.
Like hell it's funny.
What kind of person do you think I am
to kiss someone and think it's a joke?
Especially with you.
So, what now?
Should we just make things clear...
or just forget about it
and act normal,
like nothing ever happened?
How do you want it to be?
Are you okay with this?
Are you talking about...
that kiss you gave me...
or the fact that you're holding my hand?
Both.
I'm not sure.
Can I try it one more time?
♪And this time♪
♪I need you to be on my side♪
♪Be with me every second of the ride♪
♪I need to wake up right here with you♪
So, are you okay?
I'm still not sure.
I think I'll need to try it again.
(Another unexpected scandal
has hit the IT and esports industry.)
Wait, that's P'Pech.
It's a full-blown scandal for Mr. Pech,
(CEO Pech Gets Caught in a Scandal!)
CEO of a top computer hardware company.
He was caught red-handed
taking a mystery woman
who wasn't his wife to a concert.
His wife released a tearful video
exposing him for all to see.
But the scandal doesn't stop there.
Netizens have dug up...
PECHTECH's financial records
(Balance Sheet of PECHTECH Co., Ltd.)
and even looked into
its esports team, B.S. Brothers.
It was discovered the players
have been owed salaries for years,
totaling nearly a million baht.
He only started paying on time
after the team became RPL runners-up.
Honestly,
this is a serious violation
of the league's rules.
P'Pech, seriously?
Why did you have to mess around
at a time like this?
We're officially screwed.
P'Pech's secretary called me
and said that our team...
is at risk of being disqualified
from the tournament.
- What?
P'Pech's reputation in the league
is in the gutter right now.
The league management said
our team needs to
settle the debt immediately,
and we need a financial guarantee
for the players' salaries.
What the hell?
Sh*t.
Are we cursed this year or something?
Is the financial guarantee
the only option?
Isn't there any other way?
Where's P'Pech, though?
That bastard turned off his phone.
That's why
his secretary called me instead.
This is insane.
The owner's problems
have nothing to do with us!
- I'm losing it.
- This is bullsh*t.
Making a fuss won't change anything.
We need to come up with the money
or get ourselves a new team owner.
Hey.
The APL starts in less than a week.
How are we supposed to find a new owner?
We have to try, don't we?
Ten, Jack, you two come with me.
Let's talk to our old sponsors
and hit up
whatever connections we've got
to ask if they're interested
in taking over our team.
P'Toobtub, Laem, Soh.
Help me out
by calling the major sponsors.
Also, stay on standby
in case the league reaches out
with anything urgent.
Got it.
I'll handle things on this end.
Let's go, guys.
- Let's go.
- Right behind you.
I think I have their contacts.
Let me pull them up.
What are you doing?
I'm beat.
Totally exhausted.
How's it going?
The timing is just too tight.
And many companies have already
closed out their budgets.
Getting a massive sum of money
at such short notice is tough.
That's true.
I've also called quite a few places,
but none of them have gotten back to me.
It's okay.
We'll try again tomorrow, alright?
We'll find a way out of this.
What's that smell? Smells so good.
Is Chef Soh on duty today?
Whoa, what's for dinner?
Look at that.
Everything looks delicious.
Hello?
This is Soh speaking.
Who is this?
Been waiting long?
Not at all.
Okay.
Let's get down to business.
Actually, my team manager
can help your team
get to the APL in time.
Really?
Yeah.
But...
there's a catch.
Why are you guys looking so serious?
Peem?
What's his business with Soh?
People are trashing Soh
all over the internet.
They're saying
our team is falling apart.
I can't blame him
for looking for a way out.
Everyone's calling him a traitor,
saying he betrayed us.
Why are you sitting here
all alone in the dark?
What are you planning to do?
What did Peem say to you?
Blue Viper...
is going to settle our salaries for us.
And what's the price for that?
Are you the price?
Yes.
Next season, I have to join them.
I'm not letting you go.
We're on the same team, Soh.
If there's a problem,
we have to solve it together.
There's no reason
for you to sacrifice yourself like this.
It's because we are on the same team.
I don't want to see our team
in this situation.
Besides, B.S. Brothers has come so far.
Since we have this chance,
shouldn't we take it?
But what's the trade-off?
The fact that we won't have you
on our team next year?
This is probably the best way, P'Three.
We have no other choice.
Who says we don't?
How am I supposed
to come up with the money?
F*ck it.
There goes my electricity bill.
Let's use it for now.
Come on over!
Step right up, everyone!
B.S. Brothers shirts are now on sale!
They're limited edition, one-of-a-kind.
Every piece is unique
because I have no damn clue
where the screen-printing screen went.
Everyone,
come buy everything at our stall!
Hurry, hurry!
- Come on over!
- They're limited edition!
- Come on, you can take photos.
- Ten, Jack, you're so handsome!
- Can we get a photo?
- Sure.
You can take photos, everyone.
Yeah, it's fine.
But could you
support B.S. Brothers, too?
- Alright, here.
- Here, this one.
This lightstick is only 450.
And this shirt
our handsome P'Ten is holding...
is 500 baht. Pick whichever you want!
- This one's a great deal.
- You can pick anything.
Whoa, that's expensive.
Can you give us a discount?
- Too expensive?
- It's quality.
- Can you lower the price?
- Yes.
Please give us a discount.
Over here!
Only a hundred!
Everything's just a hundred baht.
Come on!
Come take a look.
You can pick what you like.
- Knockoffs come out fast these days.
- Everything's 100!
- Go ahead, pick one.
- This isn't good.
- Only a hundred.
- Hey, 99 baht over here!
Only 99 baht!
- Come on!
- Come on.
- Only 99, take your pick.
- This one's nice.
- 99 baht, hurry!
- This one is handsome.
Good.
50 baht!
- Fifty?
Fif...
50 baht?
- Take your pick, guys!
- Let me calculate the costs...
49 over here!
- 49!
- 49?
Come on, 49 baht!
One thousand nine hundred and twenty,
plus some random change.
I told you.
Don't start a price war.
Our cash flow is tight.
We're gonna go broke at this rate.
Did you learn that from a series?
Oh, come on. You can't play like that.
Here, let me carry you.
Come on, I'll carry you myself.
Oh, look at that. That hurts.
How's that? You're all crooked now.
Ow...
That's a total eyesore,
but look at this.
If you don't have
these blue-light glasses,
you won't be able to
take your eyes off me.
Do you know why?
I don't want to brag,
but look at this. These lenses
are made with space-age technology.
Look at these frames.
They're Vibranium.
You don't believe me?
You don't believe it?
You...
You don't believe me, do you?
See? You don't believe me?
Look at that!
Told you they're tough,
drop-proof, and unbreakable.
I'm not trying to flex.
Come on.
Are cooking games
this high-def these days?
Whoa, crystal clear.
This looks great. It's making me hungry.
Hungry? Let's grab a grain bar.
Here.
It's heavenly, guys.
(What's gotten into you?
Get some rest.)
(This feels like an ad now. I'm out.)
(Unfollowing you. This is too much.)
Hey, wait a sec. Don't go yet!
Why would you leave right now?
How are you guys doing?
(Look, I'm telling you...)
If you guys keep selling stuff
at this market
for a whole year,
you still won't hit a million.
You guys have to face the truth.
We really have a money problem.
As for Soh,
he's just looking out for his friends.
Hey, we're B.S. Brothers.
Are we gonna give up this easily?
I think...
we should spend
our remaining time practicing.
We still have Soh for this tournament.
As for the next one, we'll cross
that bridge when we get to it.
P'Toobtub's right.
After the APL,
we're gonna be totally lost, though.
We'll have to find a replacement for Soh
next season anyway.
It's not your time yet.
Man, then when?
And what about you, Three?
What's your move?
(You should be able to give me
your answer tonight, right?)
(I've made my decision.)
(I'll choose the best path for you)
(and for our team.)
(See you at the APL.)
In the final stretch
before the transfer window closes,
rumors are swirling that
Blue Viper is set to snatch up
legendary player Derya for their roster.
Inside sources report that
they are ready to unveil Derya
at the Blue Viper fan meeting today.
Welcome to Blue Viper, bro.
See you next season.
Okay, Soh. Now put the jacket on.
We'll go sign the contract.
Welcome.
Congratulations.
Ladies and gentlemen, the wait is over.
It's time to introduce the newest member
joining the Unbeatable Kings.
Let's have a big round of applause
for Blue Viper's new member!
Alright, now that
the introductions are over,
next up,
I'd like to ask Derya
to sign the contract right now.
(Signature)
Soh, stop!
P'Three?
Soh!
Didn't I tell you
that I can't live without you?
It's not just Three.
It's all of us.
That's right.
You can't just barge in here like this.
Security!
Over my dead body!
They're strong as hell.
Go for it, buddy!
Are you sure
this is what you want to do?
Your team is about to be disqualified
from the league.
Don't you want to compete
in the APL anymore?
Did you really think
I'd show up here without a backup plan?
I can understand
your interest in the competition,
but risking this much money
without any guarantee,
it just doesn't sound worth it.
I know, Dad.
But this money...
isn't just for me.
It's for everyone
who has fought alongside me.
Soh was even willing
to sacrifice his own future.
If I let him face this all alone,
I wouldn't deserve
to be the team captain anymore.
Dad,
I know his reputation is in the gutter.
He's stubborn.
He runs away from his problems.
He even left the family business
for me to handle all by myself,
and he just ran off to play games.
Are you actually trying to help me?
But you see it, too,
that the only thing
he's never given up on
is gaming.
And all this time,
no matter how much
of a screw-up he's been,
he's never once begged you for anything.
He's headstrong
with a big ego.
But today, a guy like him
is willing to swallow his pride.
He's begging for your help
even though this is the place
he hates the most,
yet he's doing it anyway
just so his team can keep going.
Dad...
Can you please trust my loser brother
just this once?
If your team needs a new owner,
it should be under our family name.
But I have one condition.
You have to bring
that championship home.
Understand?
Yes, Dad. I promise.
Mom, don't just stand there smiling.
Come here, Mrs. Wanphen.
It's okay.
See? He said yes.
I told you so.
(B.S. Brothers by Saenganan)
I'd like to introduce everyone to...
the new sponsor
and owner of B.S. Brothers,
Saenganan Gold Shop.
(B.S. Brothers by Saenganan)
Whoa.
You sure we're still an esports team,
not some kind of walking billboards?
Shut up, Laem.
We're lucky enough
just to have a new owner.
My apologies,
but you can't take our player anywhere
because Soh already signed the contract.
The contract is now legally binding.
Maybe not yet.
I actually hadn't finished signing it.
P'Three interrupted me.
It's still missing an H.
Sh*t...
Soh is a total savage.
Whoa, so Wimp Viper signed with P'So,
- instead of Soh.
- It's P'So now.
What the heck?
What a total waste of my damn time.
To hell with it.
We'll win even without Soh.
Let's go.
If that's what you think,
then good for you.
See you at the APL.
Bring it.
You derpy kid.
(Another shocking twist in the scene!)
(Soh has suddenly announced
his departure from Blue Viper)
(after rumors of him joining the team
lasted less than five minutes.)
(He signed the contract,
only to tear it up moments later.)
And this incident has set the stage
for the upcoming match in the APL
between the defending champs,
Blue Viper,
and the dark horse, B.S. Brothers.
I'm telling you,
it's going to be intense.
P'Three...
Thank you for not letting go of my hand.
Thank you for letting me
stand here again,
alongside everyone.
Thank you.
Whoa, look at that move!
How could I let go
of my number one Support that easily?
♪The answer is you
whenever I ask my heart,♪
♪Can't get over you
though I try so hard♪
♪I'm afraid that
love could pull us apart♪
♪If I'm the only one
who's loving with all my heart♪
♪So many times I've rehearsed the line♪
♪To tell you that I wish you were mine,♪
♪But I turn into a coward every time
you look in my eyes♪
♪Maybe the risk is too high to take,♪
♪Just being near you
is enough for my sake,♪
♪But my heart beats so fast
that I can't fake♪
♪I'll find my way
into your heart one day,♪
♪Getting a little closer every day,♪
♪Before you even look my way,♪
♪Before you realize I'm here to stay♪
♪For now,
I'll just keep things brotherly♪
♪While caring for you secretly♪
♪I'll leave no signs for you to see♪
♪Until your heart makes room for me♪